McCaddon Collection of the Barnum and Bailey Circus, 1871-1907 (bulk 1895-1905): Finding Aid TC040
Manuscripts Division
- Series 2: Scrapbooks, 1849-1968 December 19; 25 boxes
  - Scrapbook 7: Barnum & Bailey vs. Sells Bros. Opposition, 1891-1892; General (to 1935), 1 box
    - Sells Bros. anti-Ringling attack, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 94)
    - Sells Bros. anti-Wallace circus attack, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 95)
    - Article on Olympia grounds and facilities, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 100-101)
    - Drawings and tale of Barnum's "sacred" white elephant, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 102-105)
    - Article on Cooper's gift of elephant, Dunk, to American Zoological Gardens, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 106)
    - Photo of largest stand of Bills ever posted in U.S. done for Forepaugh by the American Bill Posting Co. Program from "Hoodman's Blind", dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 107)
    - Circus eulogy, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 108)
    - Photo of scenes from Forepaugh Shows, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 109)
    - Photo of Bailey, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 111)
    - Puck Cartton re: bicyclists, 1893; 1 box (Box 23, Page 112)
    - Article on Bailey and Circus, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 113)
    - Favorable article on Bailey's personal habits and character, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 114)
    - Sample letterhead. Great London Circus, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 116)
    - Sample letterhead, P.T. Barnum's Show combined with the Great London Circus, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 117)
    - Two articles commending McCaddon on his moral rectitude and exemplary behavior, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 118)
    - Ad for Forepaugh and Sells Bros. combined shows, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 119)
    - Official Barnum and Bailey routes, 1900; 1 box (Box 23, Page 120)
    - Photo of Barnum and Bailey Circus Wagon, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 121)
    - Blueprint of Winter Season layout, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 122-123)
    - Eulogy on Bailey, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 124)
    - Miscellaneous on film, "The Mighty Barnum", dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 125)
    - July 4th Commemoration, 1903; 1904; 1905; 1 box (Box 23, Page 127)
    - Photo of Madison Square Garden, 1870. Poem, celebrating Barnum, 1 box (Box 23, Page 128)
    - Death of "Old John," elephant. Ad for Gimbel's replica of Barnum's American Museum, 1935; 1 box (Box 23, Page 129)
    - "The Drunkard" revival of play produced by Barnum for his American Museum. Replica of the poster celebrating the birth of the first American elephant, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 130)
    - New stories on the circus at Olympia, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 131)
    - Bertram Mills Circus, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 132)
    - Mr. Charles Bucher recalls early days of Barnum and Bailey, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 133)
    - "Secrets of Circus Life" no. 2 by Bertram Mills, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 135)
    - "Secrets of Circus Life" no. 3 by Bertram Mills, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 136)
    - "Secrets of Circus Life" no. 4 by Bertram Mills, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 137)
    - Notice by Sells Bros. warning against other Sells circus, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 326)
    - Sells and Rentfrow Circus responds to above, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 327)
    - Article re: Sells Bros. suit against New South Wales for unnecessary quarantine and slaughter of ring horses, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 328)
    - Insulting letter to Grover Cleveland from Charles B. Stowe, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 329)
    - Sells and Rentfrow ad anti-Sells Bros, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 330)
  - Scrapbook 8: Barnum & Bailey, 1890-1891; 1 box
    - Barnum's Birthplace - House at Bridgeport - American Museum, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 24, Page 1)
    - Press Notices, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 24, Page 2)
    - Press Notices, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 24, Page 9)
    - Representatives of New York Papers visit Bridgeport, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 24, Page 10)
    - Representatives of N.Y. Papers Interview P.T. Barnum 2 months prior to death, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 24, Page 10)
    - N.Y. Press Notices, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 24, Page 11)
    - N.Y. Press Notices, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 24, Page 13)
    - Arrival of Col. Daniel Boone - From abroad with animal act, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 24, Page 13-15)
    - Preparing Advertising for Barnum & Bailey, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 24, Page 18)
    - Interview with Mrs. P.T. Barnum, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 24, Page 20)
    - Interview with P.T. Barnum, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 24, Page 21)
    - Interview with P.T. Barnum regarding "Jumbo", dates not examined; 1 box (Box 24, Page 22)
    - Description of Barnum & Bailey Posters and Advance routine, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 24, Page 23)
    - Visit to Mr. & Mrs. Barnum at Bridgeport and special long interview. His views on advertising and marriage, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 24, Page 24)
    - New York Press Notices, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 24, Page 25-29)
    - General write-up of B. & B. in Winters Quarters, 1891 March 15; 1 box (Box 24, Page 30-31)
    - General write-up of B. & B. of the work departments, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 24, Page 32)
    - Ballet girls from abroad & Legislative bills to prohibit tights, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 24, Page 33)
    - B. & B. night torchlight street parade, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 24, Page 36)
    - Training women to ride principal acts, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 24, Page 37-38)
    - Discipline rules and regulations of B. & B. shows, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 24, Page 39)
    - Arrival of the Big Show in N.Y. to open the Season of, 1891; 1 box (Box 24, Page 40-41)
    - Autobiography of P.T. Barnum published as an obituary in the N.Y. Sun 1891 March 24 just prior to his death, 1 box (Box 24, Page 42-45)
    - Barnum & Bailey Torchlight Parade, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 24, Page 46-53)
    - Barnum & Bailey Rehearsals for the N.Y. Opening, 1891 March 26; 1 box (Box 24, Page 54)
    - Barnum & Bailey, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 24, Page 55-57)
    - Barnum & Bailey Opening Press Notices, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 24, Page 58-62)
    - P.T. Barnum's Historical Society Building at Bridgeport, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 24, Page 63)
    - A Ballet Girl at Barnum's - Press story by a woman writer who joins out for one performance, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 24, Page 66-68)
    - How the Foreign Agent works and billing the Show, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 24, Page 69-70)
    - A talk with George Conklin, animal trainer. Baby McKee visits the circus - Priest Harrison's grandchild, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 24, Page 71)
    - Barnum's Spring Awakening - Illustrated American, 1891; 1 box (Box 24, Page 76-77)
    - Barnum & Bailey's Opening Review, 1891; 1 box (Box 24, Page 78-79)
    - Reminiscences of P.T. Barnum, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 24, Page 80)
    - A young trapeze lady, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 24, Page 85)
    - The three Meers Sisters - English riders, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 24, Page 86-87)
    - Reminiscences of J. A. Bailey. How Jumbo was found, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 24, Page 87-88)
    - Elephant Bill's story - Newman, who brought Jumbo over, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 24, Page 89-90)
    - How I became a clown. Chas. Conrad, Clown, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 24, Page 91)
    - P.T. Barnum's last illness, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 24, Page 93-100)
    - P.T. Barnum's death, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 24, Page 103-105)
    - Japanese Boy Performers, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 24, Page 108-110)
    - Secret of Barnum's Success by "Howard", dates not examined; 1 box (Box 24, Page 111)
    - Barnum loved children & other stories by N.Y. Times, 1891 April 12; 1 box (Box 24, Page 113-114)
    - Barnum as he was - by Bernard Peters, Journal, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 24, Page 115-116)
    - Girls in Glass Cases - Illusions, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 24, Page 117)
    - Reminiscences of Barnum, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 24, Page 119-122)
    - Barnum & Jennie Lind, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 24, Page 131-135)
    - Secrets of the Circus, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 24, Page 138-139)
    - "Barnum's lucky partners" by Ed. Kohl, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 24, Page 142)
    - "Bailey not Barnum" by John Carboy - N.Y. Dispatch, 1891 April 19. Best and most truthful account of the relations between Barnum and Bailey. "In Eulogies of the dead let us not do injustices to the living", 1 box (Box 24, Page 143-144)
    - "Caesar among Showmen" - Bailey the creator of the modern circus. Article in N.Y. Times, 1891 April 19; 1 box (Box 24, Page 146-147)
    - "What a Menagerie costs" - Interview with J. A. Bailey N.Y. Sun, 1891 April 19; 1 box (Box 24, Page 148)
    - "If you would join The Big Circus" You must sign a cast iron contract. Copy of the rules and regulations, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 24, Page 149)
    - "A Circus School" Where riders are taught, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 24, Page 151)
    - "Origin of the Stage Ghost Show", dates not examined; 1 box (Box 24, Page 151)
    - "Theatrical advertising - Clever hits that have been made N.Y. News, 1891 February 15; 1 box (Box 24, Page 153)
    - The New Madison Square Garden, 1890; 1 box (Box 24, Page 154)
    - Bill Boards and how the work is done, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 24, Page 155)
  - Scrapbook 9: J. A. Bailey and Organization of Stock Co., London, 1899; 1 box
    - Two studio photos of J.A. Bailey. News clippings from British papers Re: Barnum and Bailey's incorporation in London, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 25, Page 1-46)
    - Memorandum of Association, Barnum and Bailey, Ltd., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 25, Page 47)
  - Scrapbook 10: Barnum & Bailey, Foreign Tour, 1897-1902 (Photograph Album), 1 box
    - Chester, Eng., The beginning, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 1)
    - Driving the stakes, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 2)
    - The main guy stakes, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 3)
    - When the canvas is first up, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 4)
    - One of the chandeliers, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 5)
    - The Jacks supporting the seats, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 6)
    - The "Reserves", dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 7)
    - The folding seats, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 8)
    - How the elephants are held, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 9)
    - The animal cages, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 10)
    - The king of beasts in harmless, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 11)
    - Chester, Eng., The "lay out", dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 12-13)
    - The 40-horse team at Chester, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 14)
    - The bandwagon at Chester, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 15)
    - The elephants in Parade, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 16)
    - The equestrian section, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 17)
    - One of the gilded cages closed, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 18)
    - One of the gilded cages open, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 19)
    - The pole wagon, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 20)
    - The kennel cage, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 21)
    - The blacksmith shop, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 22)
    - The range wagon in action, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 23)
    - The healthiest stables on earth, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 24)
    - Limbering up the racers, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 25)
    - The sideshow ready, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 26)
    - The trains placed at the crossing, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 27)
    - The "runs" ready, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 28)
    - All 4 trains in the yard, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 29)
    - One pole up at Breslau, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 30)
    - Three poles up, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 31)
    - Spreading the canvas, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 32)
    - Six poles up and canvas rising, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 33)
    - Stringing electric light wires, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 34)
    - The pony stake gang, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 35)
    - Side wall in place, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 36)
    - The canvas spread at Breslau, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 37)
    - Back of the dining room, Breslau, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 38)
    - The stables at Breslau, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 39)
    - Among the horses, Breslau, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 40)
    - The elephants enjoy their luncheon, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 41)
    - Unloading under the Eiffel Tower, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 42-43)
    - The running stock ready, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 44)
    - Work horses waiting for wagons, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 45)
    - The children's pet arrives in Paris, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 46)
    - The ponies in the railway yards, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 47)
    - First American railway cars unloading in Paris, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 48)
    - The "pull-over" team at work, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 49)
    - American couplings in Europe, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 50)
    - The coupling in practice, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 51)
    - The advertising car, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 52)
    - Interior of advertising car, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 53)
    - Unloading trains at Halensee, Berlin, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 54)
    - Detraining the horses, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 55)
    - Work horses ready at the railway, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 56)
    - Arrival of the sleeping car, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 57)
    - Detraining of the elephants, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 58)
    - The Parade in Berlin, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 59-64)
    - The Woman's Circus in rehearsal, Berlin, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 65)
    - Rehearsing the elephants, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 66-69)
    - The "Freaks'" Platform, Berlin, 1900; 1 box (Box 26, Page 70)
    - Group of Freaks, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 71)
    - Groups of Freaks, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 72)
    - Parade at Southport, England, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 73-78)
    - The Parade at Cambridge, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 79-83)
    - Around the show at Cambridge, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 84-87)
    - Dining room, Indian boy, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 88)
    - Clown's Pig, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 89)
    - The pull over team, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 90)
    - Coming down the runs, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 91)
    - "Polers" at work, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 92)
    - The pull up team waiting, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 93)
    - Leaving the station, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 94)
    - The white Buffalo ready, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 95)
    - Old Fritz appears, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 96)
    - Elephants lined up, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 97)
    - Camels coming out, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 98)
    - Two-humped Beauties, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 99)
    - Stake gang at work, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 100)
    - Material on the ground, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 101)
    - Interior of Menagerie, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 102)
    - Interior of Menagerie - The Freaks, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 103)
    - Interior of Circus, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 104)
    - The tents at Geneva, 1902; 1 box (Box 26, Page 105)
    - Crowds at Lyon, France, 1902; 1 box (Box 26, Page 106-107)
    - Electric light engines glowed, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 108)
    - Electric light engines ready for work, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 109)
    - Electric light engines in action, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 110)
    - Electric light engines cleared for service, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 111)
    - Before the Paintings, Marseilles, 1902; 1 box (Box 26, Page 112)
    - The "Come out", Marseilles, 1902; 1 box (Box 26, Page 113)
    - The Show is on, Marseilles, 1902; 1 box (Box 26, Page 114)
    - From the "property" corner, Marseilles, 1902; 1 box (Box 26, Page 115)
    - "The Front", Marseilles, 1902; 1 box (Box 26, Page 116)
    - The lay out, Marseilles, 1902; 1 box (Box 26, Page 117)
    - The open-air stable, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 118)
    - In the menagerie, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 119)
    - The electric Dynamos, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 120)
    - The source of light, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 121)
    - The high power light engines, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 122)
    - The boiler as reflector, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 123)
    - The crowds at Berlin, 1900; 1 box (Box 26, Page 124-125)
    - The "big top" spread, Tours, 1902; 1 box (Box 26, Page 126)
    - The "big top" going up, Tours, 1902; 1 box (Box 26, Page 127)
    - Babe placing the wagons, Tours, 1902; 1 box (Box 26, Page 128)
    - Babe, Tours, 1902; 1 box (Box 26, Page 129)
    - Fritz' last march. Tours, 1902; 1 box (Box 26, Page 130)
    - Fritz' last sleep. Tours, 1902; 1 box (Box 26, Page 131)
    - Fritz made havoc at Tours, 1902; 1 box (Box 26, Page 132)
    - Fritz rests well. Tours, 1902; 1 box (Box 26, Page 133)
    - Good elephant at last. Tours, 1902; 1 box (Box 26, Page 134)
    - Tip doomed at Liverpool, 1898; 1 box (Box 26, Page 135)
    - "Elephant Bill's" good-bye, Liverpool, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 136)
    - Death quick and easy. Liverpool, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 137)
    - Open air show, Narbonne, 1902 May 8; 1 box (Box 26, Page 138)
    - Windy and bad holding, Narbonne, 1902 May 9; 1 box (Box 26, Page 139)
    - But the crowds with us, Narbonne, 1902 May 8; 1 box (Box 26, Page 140)
    - The Menagerie at Perpignan, 1902 May 9; 1 box (Box 26, Page 141)
    - The tents at Toulouse, 1902; 1 box (Box 26, Page 142)
    - The Front at Toulouse, 1902; 1 box (Box 26, Page 143)
    - By the river's green bank, Toulouse, 1902; 1 box (Box 26, Page 144)
    - The crowds at Manchester, 1898; 1 box (Box 26, Page 145)
    - On the "Place des Quinconces", Bordeaux, 1902; 1 box (Box 26, Page 146)
    - The front at Bordeaux, 1902; 1 box (Box 26, Page 147)
    - The heart of the city, Bordeaux, 1902; 1 box (Box 26, Page 148)
    - Bordeaux, 1902; 1 box (Box 26, Page 149-151)
    - Place de la Comédie, Bordeaux, 1902; 1 box (Box 26, Page 152-153)
    - Advance Car and its trailer, Nevers, 1902; 1 box (Box 26, Page 154)
    - Under the shadow of Pilatus, Lucerne, 1902; 1 box (Box 26, Page 155)
    - Mandarin at Lucerne, 1902; 1 box (Box 26, Page 156)
    - Under the Grand Salève, Geneva, 1902; 1 box (Box 26, Page 157)
    - Place de Plainpalais, Geneva, 1902; 1 box (Box 26, Page 158)
    - Property wagon in trouble, Lucerne, 1902; 1 box (Box 26, Page 159)
    - Baby elephant and mother, Lucerne, 1902; 1 box (Box 26, Page 160)
    - Doubling up, Lucerne, 1902; 1 box (Box 26, Page 161)
    - Deep in the mud, Thiers, France, 1902; 1 box (Box 26, Page 162)
    - The heart of Savoy. Chambery, France, 1902; 1 box (Box 26, Page 163)
    - Under the Swiss flag, Zurich, 1902; 1 box (Box 26, Page 164)
    - Advance Car at Winterthur, Switzerland, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 26, Page 165)
    - Crowds at Leeds, England, 1898; 1 box (Box 26, Page 166)
    - Bill board at Alais, France, 1902; 1 box (Box 26, Page 167)
    - A strong military guard at Béziers, 1902; 1 box (Box 26, Page 168-169)
  - Scrapbook 11: Barnum & Bailey, Foreign Tour, 1897-1902 (Photograph Album), 1 box
    - The route, 1898; 1 box (Box 27, Page 200)
    - The route, 1899; 1 box (Box 27, Page 201)
    - The route, 1900; 1 box (Box 27, Page 202)
    - The route, 1901; 1 box (Box 27, Page 203)
    - The route, 1902; 1 box (Box 27, Page 204)
    - The two young giraffes at Paris, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 27, Page 205)
    - 70-horse group. Olympia, London, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 27, Page 206)
    - The old guard. Olympia, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 27, Page 207)
    - Baby elephant. Olympia, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 27, Page 208)
    - Forty-horse team, Manchester, 1898; 1 box (Box 27, Page 209-210)
    - The Parade. Manchester, 1898; 1 box (Box 27, Page 211-212)
    - The Indian Wigwam, Manchester, 1898; 1 box (Box 27, Page 213-214)
    - Crowds watching the Manchester Parade, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 27, Page 215)
    - The main entrance in Hungarian, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 27, Page 216)
    - Mr. Bailey among his wild Hungarians, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 27, Page 217)
    - The front at Budapest, 1901; 1 box (Box 27, Page 218)
    - Sideshow Paintings. Budapest, 1901; 1 box (Box 27, Page 219)
    - Types of Hungarians. Budapest, 1901; 1 box (Box 27, Page 220)
    - The railway yards at Budapest, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 27, Page 221)
    - After the show had begun. Budapest, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 27, Page 222)
    - Two bright young Hungarians (Barts) Budapest, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 27, Page 223)
    - Rehearsing the Spectacle, Paris, 1902; 1 box (Box 27, Page 224-228)
    - Among the Ballet, Paris, 1902; 1 box (Box 27, Page 229-233)
    - Among the Propertie. Galerie des machines. Paris, 1901-1902; 1 box (Box 27, Page 234-236)
    - Norton Smith before the military officers. Paris, 1901; 1 box (Box 27, Page 237-240)
    - Smith lets on steam, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 27, Page 241)
    - The horse subdued, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 27, Page 242)
    - The Cook Tent. Breslau, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 27, Page 243)
    - Guarded by one of France's heroes. Brives, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 27, Page 244)
    - The open-air dining room. Brives, France, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 27, Page 245-246)
    - The guard of Soldiers, Brives, France, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 27, Page 247)
    - We closed the theatre doors at Brives, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 27, Page 248)
    - The Salle des Fetes, Paris, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 27, Page 249)
    - Sunday before the Galerie des Machines, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 27, Page 250)
    - A visit from the King of Greece, Chambery, France, 1902 August 14; 1 box (Box 27, Page 251-254)
    - Breton peasants at Quimper, France, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 27, Page 255-260)
    - Elephants bathing at Chumont, France, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 27, Page 261-263)
    - Mother and baby elephant, 1902; 1 box (Box 27, Page 264)
    - Open air show. Angouleme, France, 1902 June 2; 1 box (Box 27, Page 265-266)
    - Horses in the Ocean at St. Malo, France, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 27, Page 267)
    - At St. Malo's fashionable beach, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 27, Page 268)